Guide to the Records of John Brademas Speeches 1965-1991 RG 3.0.10 RG 3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Exec. Committee/ Trustees, NYU, Trip to Japan, Hong Kong, Thailand, India, Nepal, Jap. Center at NYU, Trip to Aspen & Portland, Dental & Medical Center, Update, Fundraising, Sep 20, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254618
  - Student Meeting, NYU, (Talking Points, Enrollment/Financial Aid, Budget Cuts, Housing and Security, Wash. Square News, NYU Goals), Sep 25, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Bureaucratic Democracy-"The Search for Democracy & Efficiency in American Governmen", Cambridge, MA, (By Douglas Yates) --Files Missing, Sep 27, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Exec. Committee, NYU, (Trip to Japan, Hong Kong, Thailand, India, Nepal, Jap. Center at NYU, Trip to Aspen & Portland, Dental & Medical Center, Update, Fundraising), Sep 30, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Borges Luncheon/New York Institute for the Humanities, NYU, (Background of Institute, Borges, Brademas & Spanish Interests), Oct 1, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - St. Francis of Assisi 8th Centenary Celebration, NYU, (Appeal of St. Francis), Oct 5, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - "Annual Dinner of the American Assoc. of Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, Pierre Hotel NY, (Brademas' & Israel, While in Congress, International Exchanges & Education)", Oct 5, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - GBA Tel Aviv Reception, Tel Aviv Univ. Israel, ( Dr. Haim Ben-Shahar, U.S. & Israel, NYU & Israel, NYU & Tel-Aviv Exchange Program, International Educ.), Oct 7, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Gallatin Assoc. Dinner, Waldorf, Astoria NY, (John Loeb, Gallatin Contributions, NYU in General), Oct 7, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - WCBS Interview on "Public Hearing", NY, (Brademas' First Year at NYU, NYU Background, Higher Education), Oct 8, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - GBA Annual Alumni Awards Dinner, NYU Club, ( Brademas Japan Trip, State of Univ., Future of NYU), Oct 13, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Univ. Senate Meeting Brademas Remarks, NYU, (Board of Trustees, Meeting, Faculty, Brademas' Trip to Japan,Hong Kong, Thailand, India, Nepal, Medical Center Needs & Goals, Financial Aid, Brademas on Various Boards, Update on NYU Schools), Oct 14, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Friends of Town Hall Award Dinner, NYU Club, (Gerald Schoenfeld), Oct 17, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees Report, NYU, (Faculty, Brademas' Trip to Japan,Hong Kong, Thailand, India, Nepal, Medical Center Needs & Goals, Financial Aid, Brademas on Various Boards, Update on NYU Schools), Oct 18, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council Exec. Committee, NYU, (Faculty Convocation, Brademas' Ideas for the Administration & Management of NYU, Brademas' Gov. & Bus. Affilliations), Oct 21, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Law School Alumni Day/Carey Citation, NYU, (Fundraising Record & Goals, Jacob Javits, Carey, Carey & Brademas in Congress), Oct 23, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Parent's Day, NYU, (Remarks Concerning Each School at NYU, NYU in General, Student Aid), Oct 24, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Opening Session of the National Forum of the College Board, Waldorf, Astoria NY,(Reagan Admin./Budget Cuts, Renewed Interest in Education, New Federalism, Public Schools), Oct 27, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Fifth Avenue Association, Waldorf-Astoria, NY, (New York City, NYU, Bus. & Educ.), Oct 27, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Dental Associates Dinner, St. Regis, Sherton, NY, (Financial Aid, Faculty), Oct 27, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Archbishop Iakovos High School Dinner, Jamica, NY, (Cyprus Greek Clubs at NYU, Importance of Education, Bi-lingual Educ., Iakovas), Oct 29, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Greek High School Parents Conference St. Demetrios High School, Astoria, NY, (Cyprus Greek Clubs at NYU, Importance of Education, Bi-lingual Educ.), Oct 30, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Louis Marshall Memorial Dinner, Jewish Theological Seminary, Plaza Hotel, NY ( Israel, Past History of Seminary, Reagan Admin., Classification of Gov. Documents, Nat'1 Archives), Oct 31, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Tisch Faculty Convocation-Tisch & Brademas Remarks, (Value of Faculty, Fundraising, International Educ., Enorllment, Reagan Admin.), Nov 1, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Council on International Education Annual Conference, NYU (Tisch Hall), ( Educational & Cultural Exchange, Brademas' International Education Act), Nov 3, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Associates Dinner, St. Regish Sheraton Hotel, NY, (BPA, Univ./Business & Industry), Nov 8, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - IFA Trustees Meeting, NYU, (Importance of IFA, Search for Director of IFA, Fundraising), Nov 8, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Pressure Group Attacks on Free Speech- 92nd St. Y. & NY Civil- Liberties Union, 92nd St. Y, NY, ( Campaign Laws/Political Contributions, Christian Voice, Nat'1 Christian Action, Coalition, Political Action Committees, Bills Brademas Introduced Re: Family Servies), Nov 9, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - NYU Alumnae Club, Woman of Achievement Award, NYU, (Grace Glueck/Art Critic, Dr. Brademas' & Legislation for the Arts), Nov 9, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Council/Exec. Committee Mtg., NYU, (Talking Points, Faculty Convocation, Election '82), Nov 10, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Univ. Senate Remarks, NYU, (Faculty Convocation, Parents Day, Anti-Discrimination Policy/ Military Recruitment at Law School, Enrollment, Financial Aid), Nov 11, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - NYU Alumni Assoc. of Southern Calif. Award/Dinner Dance for Oliva, Los Angeles, CA, (Goals of NYU), Nov 13, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Robert Wagner Archives John Sessions Memorial Award Presentation, NYU, (Dr. Brademas/Labor, Resources & Future of Archives), Nov 17, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - "New School Inauguration of Jonathan Faton As President, New School, (Higher Educ.) ", Nov 18, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Institute of Judical Administration Dinner Arthur T. Vanderbilt, Sheraton Center, (Vanderbilt/Justice), Nov 18, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Keidanren Kaikan., Tokyo, Japan (Proposal for Japanese Center at NYU), Nov 22, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Japanese Alumni Reception, NYU, (Resources at NYU & Suitability of Jap.Center at NYU), Nov 22, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Student Financial Aid -- Handbook Foreword, ( Dr. Brademas' Contribution to Financial Programs While in Congress), Nov 29, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Dean's Lunch Honoring Phillip Johnson & Richard Foster (Library), NYU, (Library Resources), Nov 29, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Blum Presidential Citation at SEHNAP, NYU, (The Handicapped), Dec 1, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Commerce Dean's Day, NYU, (Fundraising Goals), Dec 4, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting in Washington Square, (Holiday Greetings), Dec 9, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - "Tisch Preview -Speech for Dr. Brademas, TSOA, (Arts)", Dec 9, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Tisch Preview- Speech for Dean Openheim, TSOA, (Description of Bldg.), Dec 9, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Memo from Dr. Brademas to the Domestic Policy Study Group Center for National Policy, (Reagan Admin., Economy/National & Educ), Dec 10, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Dept. of Econ. Reception for Dr. Fritz Machlup, NYU, (Machlup Comments), Dec 14, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Leon Shimkin Reception, NYU, (Shimkin's Career & Commitment to NYU, Renovation of Judson Hall), Dec 14, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Faculty Council, Exec. Committee Mtg, NYU, (Copyright Suit, Financial Matters, Development Campaign, New Board Members, TSOA Preview, Cuomo Task Force), Dec 16, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Afro-American Affairs Reception (Dr. Brademas Remarks), (International Educ., Student Aid), Dec 21, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - SEHNAP (Dr. Brademas Remarks), NYU, (NYU in General, Fundraising, Teacher Training), Dec 21, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - 35th Anniversary of the Fulbright Program in Greece, Athens, Greece, (Fulbright Programs, International Education), Jan 12, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Athens College Reception, --Files Missing, Athens, Greece, Jan 13, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Advisory Council Executive Management Training in Athens Program, Athens, Greece, (Subjects within Program), Jan 13, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - New York Federal Exec. Bd., Vista Hotel, ( American Political System, Congress/Bureaucracy, Fed. Gov. & Private Institutions), Jan 19, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Radio Interview on Education Commission, WCBS, (Commission, Financial Aid, Labor Market, Student Choice of College, Scholars, Future Needs of Educ.), Jan 19, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - NY Federal Executive Board, Vista Hotel, NY, (U.S. Economic Policy), Jan 19, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Remarks of Larry Tisch at the Federal Reserve Dinner, Regency Hotel, NY, (Dr. Brademas), Jan 19, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Humphrey Award/Metropolitan Social Studies Conference, New York Hilton, NY, (Humphrey, Brademas Support for Educ. While in Congress, Reagan Admin,/"New Federalism"), Jan 22, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Badinter Citation, NYU, (French Center, Badinter's Career), Jan 22, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Dr. Brademas' Remarks at Dinner Honoring JB, Los Angeles, (Support for the Arts), Jan 27, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Preston R. Tisch's Remarks at L.A. Dinner Honoring JB, Los Angeles, (TSOA), Jan 27, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Southern California Association for Philanthropy, Los Angeles, CA (Leaders of Bus. & Industry, Public Alliance, Execellence in Educ., Faculty, Student Aid, Academic Expenses, Foundation & Corporate Support), Jan 28, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254626
  - Alumni Federation Board of Director's Meeting, NYU Club, (Fundraising Goals, Annual Giving Famous Alumni), Feb 1, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Draft Registration & Student Aid Statement, NYU, (Criticisms of Draft/Registration), Feb 2, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School of Public Admin (GPA), NYU, (Altshuller Appt.(GPA Press Release in Folder)), Feb 3, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Board of Trustees, NYU, ( Albany/Wash, Registration, Grad. Study, Badinter Lecture-(French Minister of Justice), Faculty Handbook, Fundraising/Greece Calif., Phonathon, Cuomo, Reagan, Bio of Altshuller & Berman, Feb 7, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Remarks - Brademas Univ. Senate, NYU, (Albany/Wash, Registration, Grad. Study, Badinter Lecture-(French Minister of Justice), Faculty Handbook, Fundraising/Greece Calif., Phonathon), Feb 10, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Touche Ross Roundtable/Mgt of Higher Education, Plaza Hotel, NY (Overview, Depressed Economy, Demographics, Tuition, Enrollment, Feb 14, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Exec. Committee - Faculty Council Meeting, NYU, (Talking Points, Altshuler, Berman, West 3rd St., Grad. Educ), Feb 15, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Calude Montana/Berdorf Benfit for Grey Gallery- Briefing Points, Armory, NY, (Only file in folder is a memo containing), Feb 15, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Men's Varsity Basketball Press Conf., NYU, (Resumption of Men's Basketball, Cole's, NCAA, Former Star Players), Feb 17, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Belfer Luncheon, Palm Beach, FL (NYU (Indirect Solicitation), Feb 20, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Dean Stedman Dinner, Penthouse, (Adult Education, SCE), Feb 24, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - LBJ Symposium for FDR 50th Anniv., Univ. of Texas, (FDR, LBJ & JB's Role In Education), Mar 4, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gallatin Vice-Chairmen & Deans Breakfast, NYU, (Fundraising Campaign), Mar 7, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Cunningham Arts & Salute Dinner, Plaza Hotel, NY (Support for the Arts), Mar 7, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Luncheon - Announcing Dev. Campaign, NYU, (Fundraising Goals), Mar 8, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Campaign Kickoff - Press Conf. (Fundraising), NYU, (Fundraising, Goals, Remarks by Olivia, Tisch, Heyman), Mar 8, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - New Fund Raising Luncheon, NYU, (Goals, Areas of Univ. Where Funds are Needed), Mar 8, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Politicians-in-Residence Panel --Files Missing, Meyer Hall, NY, Mar 10, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Brademas - Univ. Senate, NYU, (Admissions, Fundraising, Draft Registration, Athletics, Phonathon, Scholarships), Mar 10, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Haig/Public Policy Lecture "The Making of Foreign Policy" ,NYU, (Welcome Remarks, Importance of Lecture Series), Mar 10, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 1983 NEA Higher Education Conference, Washington, DC, (Gov. Record of Aid to Educ., Renewed Interest in Educ, Reagan Admin, Univ. & Public Schools, Univ. & Industry), Mar 11, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Brademas/Trustees, NYU, (Fundraising, Admissions, Athletics, Altshuler-Berman McCredie, Grad. Study Programs-"Genius Grants", Draft Registration), Mar 14, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - War, Peace & News Media, NYU, (Public Access to Gov.Info), Mar 18, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - GBA Alumni Conf., NYU, (State of Univ.Leadership, Med. Ctr. Research & Scholarship, Enrollment, Fundraising), Mar 19, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Catalan Week Launch, NYU, (Brademas & NYU's Interest in Spanish Culture & Studies), Mar 21, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kaplan Center Dedication, NYU Med. Ctr., (Kaplan's Contributions to Med. Center, Fundraising), Mar 22, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Altshuler Dinner, Penthouse, (GPA), Mar 24, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Colloquium/Catalonia in Modern Spain, NYU, (Brademas' Concern Re: Spanish Affairs, NYU & Spanish Studies), Mar 24, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - At the City Club of New York, CUNY Graduate Center, (International Program's at NYU, University & Community, Reagan Admin./Budget Cuts), Mar 25, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Archons of the Ecumenical Patriarchate Annual Banquet, Waldorf Astoria, NY, ( Survival of Ecumenical Patriarchate in Turkey, Amer., Greek & Turkish Relations, Greek Amer.Influence on Events), Mar 26, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Prof. Gay Wilson Allen Reception, (Allen's Career as Teacher, Emerson, Whitman), Apr 4, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Joseph Lubin Memorial ( Tributes to Lubin), Apr 7, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Gallatin Fellows Dinner --Files Missing, Apr 21, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Rabbit Morris Lieberman Memorial Lecture, Baltimore Hebrew Cong., Balt., MD, ( Jewish, Christian Relations, Int'1 Ed. & Research, U.S. Security Policy, Anti-Americanism, Reagan Admin - Arms Control, Pub. & Congressional Access to Gov. Info), Apr 23, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Reading for the Blind Awards, Yale Club, (Overcoming Handicaps), Apr 27, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Giscard d'Estaing Lecture, NYU, (NYU's Contribution to French Studies), Apr 27, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Great Teacher Awards, NYU, (Value & Qualities of Great Teachers), Apr 28, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - BU Conference on Arts & Education- "Sailing Against the Wind", Boston University, (Reagan Admin., Budget Cuts, Society & The Arts, Fundraising), Apr 29, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Senate Remarks - Univ., NYU, (Founders Day, Califano/"Politicizing God & Science", Solomen Amend. Re: Draft, Balance of Sub. Matter, Joseph Califano, Galway Kinnel, Japanese & Amer. Business, Admissions, Alumni Fed., Hon. Degrees), May 5, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - James C. Finlay Higher Education Commission, NY Assembly, (Tuition & Enrollment), May 6, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - GPA Alumni "Public & Private Sectors", NYU, (Reciprocal Advantages Re: Education & Business), May 9, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Brademas/Trustees- NYU Board of Trustees Meeting, NYU, (Joseph Califano, Galway Kinnel, Japanese & Amer. Business, Admissions, Alumni Fed., Hon. Degrees), May 9, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - American Jewish Committee Dinner Bestowing the Herbert H. Lehman Award on Martin Lipton. Grand Hayat Hotel, NY, (Interest in $ Importance of Educ., Reagan Administration), May 10, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies of New York, Regency Hotel, NY, (Reagan Admin.,Social Conditions, Foundations, Voluntarism), May 10, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Humanities- Claremont Univ. (The Presidents Forum Engaging a Whole World: The Humanitis in the 1980's), Claremont, CA, (Humanities: Problems & Solutions Re:Enrollment & Faculty, Reagan Admin), May 13, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Exercises Claremont Graduate College, Claremont, CA,, (Gov: Decisions & Policies- Re: Defense, Security, Arms Control)), May 14, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Dean Griffiths Dinner, NYU Club, (Dean Contributions to NYU, Education, SEHNAP, Public Alliance), May 20, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Council on Economic & Fiscal Priorities (Cuomo) --Files Missing, New York, May 20, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Reagan Remarks at Seton Hall, South Orange, NJ, (America: Past-Future Views on Gov. Aid to Educ.), May 21, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Commencement Exercises SUNY, Albany, (Cuomo, Gov. Support for Educ. Technology), May 22, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Bobst Third Floor Wing Dedication, Bobst, (Gifts to Library), May 23, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Annual Alumni Dinner, NYU Club, (Fundraising), May 24, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees --Files Missing, NYU, (Housing, Admissions, Honorary Degree), May 31, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, NYU, (Paul Volcker, Milton Petrie, Ieoh Ming Pei, Robert Penn Warren, Barbara McClintock, Lewis Thomas), Jun 2, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Medical Commencement (Koch), Lincoln Center, (Welcome Remarks/Koch, NYU Med. Ctr. & Bellevue), Jun 2, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - NYU Commencement, NYU, (Paul Volcker, Milton Petrie, Ieoh Ming Pei, Robert Penn Warren, Barbara McClintock, Lewis Thomas), Jun 3, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Lowell Commencement, Lowell, MA (Education, Congressional Background, 1984 Election), Jun 4, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - National State Budget Officers, Albany, NY (Econ. Dev. Through Public/Private Partnership), Jun 7, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - NASBO, Jun 7, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    bar code: 3 1142 042254634
  - Pell Introduction, Washington DC, (Pell's Contribution to the Arts), Jun 9, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Intern Program, Washington DC, (Value of Internship, Similarities of JB's Responsibilities as Congressman & NYU President), Jun 9, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Portage Lodge Dinner --Files Missing, South Bend, Ind., Jun 11, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rev. Boardman W. Kathan, NYU, (Religious Education), Jun 14, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Life Gallatin Reception, NYU, (NYU/Gallatin Fundraising), Jun 14, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Omicron Kappa Epsilon, Essex House, NY, (Dental Education, Cost of Education in General, Government Funds for Educ., Graduate Educ./ Sub-Committee), Jun 15, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The Dunes, (Dr. Brademas' Intro for Schaeffer & Franklin's book "Duel for the Dunes" (Land Conversation)), Jun 23, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Communications Technology in Education & Training, (What Each School at NYU Offers in the Area of Communications, Arrival of Computer Age, Computer in Education, Challenges of Computer Age, Directions for the Future), Jun 27, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Birkbeck College, London, (American System of Gov., Effects Upon Foreign Policy), Jun 30, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Lifelong Learning Leaders Retreat Report --Files Missing, (Interest In & Growth of Continuing Educ.), Jul 1, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Modern Greek Symposium --Files Missing, NYU, (Welcome Remarks), Oct 27, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Assoc. Of Indepen. Colleges & Universities --Files Missing, NJ, (Education, Independent Colleges, Oct 28, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Bobst 10th Anniversary, Bobst, (Library in General, Comments Re: Contributions to NYU; Jim Hester, Former NYU Pres; Mrs. Bobst, Dr. Coles, Mrs. Barry, Mr. Fisher. Awards to Alfred Koff, Kenneth Burke, Denise Levertov, Arthur Miller, Russel Baker, Bernard Malamud, John Lindsay), Nov 2, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - International Education in US Contents of Files are Missing (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Parent's Day Receptions, NYU, (Parent & Child, Comments Concerning Each School, NYU in General), Nov 6, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Trustees Scholars Dinner, NYU, (Honoring the Trustees Scholar, Importance of Education), Nov 9, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Chet Huntiey Memorial Lecture Dinner, NYU, (Welcome Remarks, Background of Lecture Series, Various Areas of Communicative Study at NYU), Nov 10, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Phi Betta Kappa Ceremony, NYU, (JB's Opinions of Club & Members), Nov 17, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Atlantic Institute for Intn'l Affairs, Washington, DC, (American Foreign Policy & Relations), Nov 18, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Cyprus Childrens Fund Dinner, NY Hilton, (Tribute to Archbishop Iakovos, Turkey's Invasion of Cyprus), Nov 18, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - High Schools & Universities, Washington, (Education, Public Policy & the Reagan Admin.), Nov 22, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Day at BPA International Banking System (1st of Lubin Lecture Series), NYU, (JB Welcome Remarks, Roles of Bus. & Educ.), Dec 3, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - King of Spain Convocation, NYU, (JB Welcome Remarks, International Educ., Spanish Americans, King's Leadership), Dec 6, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - King of Spain Convocation & Dinner, NYU, (Tisch's Welcome Remarks) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Smithsonian (Orwell), Smithsonian Inst. ("The Road After 1984/High Tech & Human Freedom" Spanish Anarchism), Dec 8, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Smithsonian Symposium, Museum of American History, (Liberal Arts, Revitalization of Humanities), Dec 8, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Network Press Conference & Board Meeting, NYU, (Promote Humanities), Dec 13, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Change Magazine Article, (Commission Findings), Jan 13, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Upward Bound Press Conference, New York, (Grant to Metro Center), Jan 24, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Little Forum's Annual Dinner, New York, (Gran to Metro Center), Jan 26, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Annual Midwinter Conference of the New York State Council of School Superintendents, Albany, (High School-University Connections), Jan 29, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, NYU, (Remarks to High Students on Study at NYU), Feb 4, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Videotape, New York, (Federal Role in Education), Feb 6, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Graduate & Professional Financial Aid Council, Virginia, (Graduate Education), Feb 14, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Japanese Chamber of Commerce of NY Lunch, New York, (Japanese Philanthrophy), Feb 23, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Dr. Robert M. Warner Dinner, NYU, (National Archives), Feb 23, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - New Trustees Dinner, NYU, (Introduction of New Trustees), Feb 28, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Opening Dinner for Picasso Exhibit, New York, (Brief Remarks), Feb 29, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Society of Foreign Consuls, New York, (United States Government), Mar 4, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - University Senate Meeting, NYU, (Status of University), Mar 8, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Trustees-Faculty Council Reception, NYU, (Greetings), Mar 12, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Real Estate Institute Annual Urban Leadership Award Dinner, NYU, (Real Estate Institute), Mar 14, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Fuqua/Wright Lunch, Washington DC, (Graduate Education), Mar 14, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Conference on Education: Action for Interaction, Connecticut, (Commission Findings), Mar 15, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Public Affairs Forum PH Dinner, NYU, (Talking Points), Mar 15, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Middle States Dinner, NYU, (Welcome of Middle States Evaluation Teams to NYU), Mar 18, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education Committee on Education & Labor, Washington DC, (Findings of National Commission on Graduate Education), Mar 19, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)